Joey...?
Oh, my God.
Okay.
So, uh...
( sighs )
I guess we should make it
official, huh?
Uh, look Rach, I...
Hey, Ross is here!
Hey, look, it's
my good friend Ross!
Hey, Ross.
Hey, Joey.
ROSS:
Hey, you.
Look, and he
brought flowers.
Oh, thanks, Ross.
I'm really more
of a candy kind of guy.
( exaggerated chuckle )
You're weird today.
Listen, I, uh...
I wanted to talk
to you about something.
Yeah, actually
I kind of need
to talk to you, too.
Uh, Joey, can you give us
just a minute?
No.
What?
I'm sorry.
I meant... no.
Hey.
Look who's here.
Where's my granddaughter?
I've been practicing
my magic tricks.
He pulled a quarter
out of my ear.
Hey, where's Mom?
She went to pick up
Aunt Liddy.
Oh, Aunt Liddy's coming?
That means we get
five dollars each!
So when do I get
to meet Emma
and show her this?
Okay, wow.
Uh, Dad, Emma's
in the nursery.
I'll take you now
if you want.
But I really want
to talk to you.
I know.
I still need to talk to you.
But before
you guys do that
I need to talk to you
and, Ross, I need
to talk to you.
Oh, and I need to talk to you.
About what?
See if you know what
these guys
are talking about.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
MONICA:
Isn't she beautiful?
Look at her.
My first grandchild.
What about Ben?
Well, of course Ben.
I meant my first
granddaughter.
( mouthing )
Oh, Ross.
Hmm?
Have you thought
any more about
you and Rachel?
Oh, yeah, actually
I was going to talk
to her when you guys
all came in the room.
Yay! That's so exciting.
You could have done
that with us there.
Yeah, right.
Oh, sure, okay.
You can touch yourself
in front of us
but you can't
talk to Rachel.
What?!
When have I ever
touched myself
in front of you guys?
Oh, please.
Just before when
you were asleep
in the lounge.
That Armenian family
was watching you
instead of the TV.
That reminds me--
that Mr. Hosmigian still
has my Gameboy.
( whispering ):
Hey, Chandler, can I
talk to you for a second?
Sure.
Dude, I just did
something terrible.
That was you?
I thought it was Jack.
No, no, that was Jack.
No. Rachel thinks
I asked her to marry me.
What? Why does
she think that?
Because it kind
of looked like I did.
Again, what?
Okay, well, I was down
on one knee
with the ring
in my hand...
As we all are
at some point
during the day.
It wasn't my ring.
It fell out
of Ross's jacket
and when I knelt down
to pick it up
Rachel thought
I was proposing.
Ross had a ring?
And he was going to propose?
I guess.
And you did it first?
This is going to kill him.
You know how much
he loves to propose.
I know, I know.
It's awful.
Well, what did she say?
She said yes.
Does Ross know?
Oh, my God.
What the hell am
I going to tell him?
Well, maybe you don't
have to tell him anything.
Ooh, I like that. Yeah.
If you clear things
up with Rachel
then Ross never needs
to find out
but you have to do
it now before he
hears about it
and kicks your ass.
Let's not get carried away.
I want a baby.
Honey, we've
been over this.
I need to be facing
the other way.
Come on.
If we have sex again
it'll double our chances
of getting pregnant.
I think that closet's
still available.
I am so tired.
Yeah, okay, but no foreplay.
Deal.
Dad, seriously!
You know,
you really should
see someone
about that.
Noted.
I want to go talk
to Rachel for a minute.
Are you going to be
okay alone for a bit?
Are you kidding me?
I could stay and look
at her forever.
Actually, uh...
Hey.
Hi.
Are you all right?
Um... I...
I think I just
got engaged.
Oh, my God! He did it?
Did you know he was
going to ask me?
Are you kidding?
I'm like the one
who talked him into it.
I like to think
of myself
as the puppet master
of the group.
And you really think
this is a good idea?
I just talked him into it.
Don't tell me
I have to do you, too.
The puppet master
gets tired, people.
I don't know.
It just doesn't
feel right.
Why? You two are so meant
to be together.
Everybody thinks so.
Really?
Even Ross?
Especially Ross.
Oh, uh, hey, Pheebs.
You know what?
I'll... I'll
come back later.
Wow, kind of a
full house here.
I guess I'll just...
I'll come back.
There he goes.
Your fiancé.
I guess so.
Although he does play
with himself in his sleep.
Can't say I'm surprised.
Dad, what
are you doing?
I think there are people
in there having sex.
Can't be me.
I'm standing right here.
Want to peek?
No!
Come on!
You know what?
I don't like you
without Mom.
Come on.
We're not peeking?
Well, I'm peeking.
Oh, my God!
CHANDLER:
Hello, sir.
You know Monica.
( mouthing )
Hey, uh, is it
okay to come in?
Of course.
Oh, Joey, this ring...
I... it's beautiful.
I love it.
Yeah, uh, look, Rach
there's something
I got to tell you.
( knocking )
Hey.
Hi.
Are you ready to try
nursing again?
Yeah.
Hi, Emma.
Hey, why do you think
she won't take my breast?
It's all right, honey.
Takes some babies
a while to get it.
But don't worry,
it'll happen.
Yowza.
RACHEL:
Okay, sweetie
you can do it.
Just open up
and put it in
your mouth.
Dear Lord.
I'm sorry, honey,
what were you saying?
Uh, uh, yeah, look,
I-I think that...
Oh, 'cause look,
she's pulling away again.
Do you think my nipples
are too big for her mouth?
She looks scared.
Doesn't she look scared?
You know, I don't
really know her.
Why don't we try
massaging the breast
to stimulate the flow.
Are you kidding me?
Oh, it's just
so frustrating.
She doesn't she
want my breast?
I don't know,
maybe she's crazy!
Oh, hey, wait up.
Hi.
Congratulations.
I didn't want to say
anything in front of Joey
'cause I didn't know
if he knew yet.
What, that we had
a baby?
Let's give him
a little credit.
Although he did eat a piece
of plastic fruit earlier.
No, no, that you and Rachel
are engaged.
What?
Oh, it's a secret?
Oh, goody. Yes.
Ooh, we haven't done
the secret thing
in a long time.
Phoebe, there is
no secret, okay?
I didn't propose.
Are you lying?
Is this like that time
you tried to convince us
you were a doctor?
I am a doctor!
You know what?
I'm just going to go
and talk to Rachel myself.
All right, me, too.
Shh.
Should we wake
her up?
No, no. Come on,
let her sleep.
She's so exhausted.
And so engaged.
( hums dramatic phrase )
Oh, my God!
She... she thinks we're engaged!
Why, why, why would she
think we're engaged?
Perhaps because you gave
her an engagement ring?
You know, Ross, doctors are
supposed to be smart.
I didn't give
her that ring.
You didn't?
No.
So whose ring is it?
It's mine.
Is it an engagement ring?
Yes.
But you didn't
give it to her?
No.
But you were going
to propose?
No!
Huh. I might be
losing interest in this.
Look... look, my mom
gave me that ring
because she wanted me
to propose to Rachel
but all I wanted
to do is see if
she maybe kind of wanted to
start things up again.
Oh, what beautiful
lukewarm sentiment.
Look, I didn't want
to rush into anything.
And it seemed like
she didn't want to either.
But I don't
understand how...
how any of this happened.
What, did she find
the ring in my jacket--
assume I was going to propose--
throw it on and just start
telling people?
No, no, she said you
actually proposed to her.
Well, I didn't!
I didn't propose!
Unless...
Did I?
I haven't slept in 40 hours
and...
...it does sound like
something I would do.
Look, we can't stay
in here forever.
Oh, I still can't
believe that
my dad saw us
having sex.
He didn't make it
to one of my piano recitals
but this, he sees.
This is okay.
We're all adults here.
There's nothing
to be ashamed of.
Now let's put
our underwear
in our pockets
and walk out the door.
Hi, Dad.
I can still call
you that, right?
Of course.
I'll always be your dad.
I just want you to know
that what you witnessed
in there
that wasn't for fun.
It wasn't fun?
Why, why, why would you...?
Look, I just don't
want you to think that
we're animals who do it
whenever we want.
I don't think that.
Before today, I never thought
of you two having sex at all.
It was a simpler time.
The truth is, Dad,
we're trying.
What?
We're trying
to get pregnant.
Oh, my God,
this is so exciting!
Well, get back in there!
I'll guard the door!
It's okay, Dad.
We can wait
until later.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I don't think so.
Aren't you ovulating?
Daddy?!
Well, you got to get at it,
Princess.
When your mother and I
were trying to conceive you
whenever she was ovulating,
bam, we did it.
That's how I got my bad hip.
That's funny.
This conversation's how
I got the bullet hole
in my head.
This one time
I had my knee up on the sink
and your mother, she was...
Daddy, I don't
think we need to hear
about the specific
positions you and
mom had sex.
You're right.
This is about your positions.
Now, what I saw in the closet
is not the optimum position
for conceiving a child,
although it might feel good.
I don't feel good right now.
But pleasure is important
and it helps
if the woman has an orgasm.
You up to the task, sailor?
Seriously, sir, my brains?
All over the wall.
Hey.
I need to tell you something.
Well, now's a good time.
I'm on my way to have
my ears cut off.
Joey asked me
to marry him.
What?
Joey proposed to me.
Is he crazy?
You just had Ross's baby.
I said yes.
What, are you crazy?
You just had Ross's baby.
It's so inappropriate.
It's worse than that.
It is wrong.
It's... It is bigger than mine.
I know.
Days of Our Lives,
thank you very much.
You can't marry him.
Why not?
I don't want to do
this alone
and he's such a sweet guy
and he loves me so much.
Do you love him?
Sure.
Sure?
Yeah, I mean, whatever.
Honey, the question is...
do you really want
to marry Joey?
No. No, I don't.
Could you be a dear
and go tell him?
You still haven't told Rachel
you weren't really proposing?
No. She had
the ring on
she seemed so excited
and then she took
her breast out.
Joey, you have to tell her
what's going on.
And what did it look like?
I didn't look at it.
Stupid baby's head
was blocking most of it.
Go and tell Rachel
right now
before Ross finds out.
It's not that easy.
She said she wanted
to marry me.
I don't want to hurt her.
Okay, look,
just do it gently.
You're right.
I'll go tell her now
before Ross finds out
and I'll be gentle.
I can do that.
I am a gentle person.
Oh, by the way
two people screwing
in there
if you want
to check that out.
Hey.
Listen, I, um...
I heard about
the engagement.
Surprised?
And confused.
Rach, sweetie, I, um...
I didn't propose to you.
I know.
I don't think you do.
You didn't propose to me.
Joey did.
Poor baby, you're so tired.
Rach, I didn't
propose to you
Joey didn't
and Chandler didn't
propose to you.
Uh...
you didn't propose
to me
Chandler didn't
propose to me
but Joey did.
Joey proposed to you?
I can come back.
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Joey, did you
propose to her?
No.
Yes, you did.
Actually, technically,
I didn't.
Well, then why did
you give me a ring?
Wait. You gave her
the ring?
No, no, and I did not
ask her to marry me.
Yes, you did!
No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
Yes, you did
and don't you say
you didn't!
( groans )
He was right there.
He got down on one knee
and he proposed.
Whoa, you were down
on one knee?
Yeah, yeah,
that looks bad.
But I didn't...
I didn't propose.
Then what did happen?
Yeah, what did happen?
The ring fell
on the floor
and I went down
to pick it up
and you thought
I was proposing.
Yeah, but you said,
"Will you marry me?"
No, I didn't.
Yes, you did!
Yes, you did.
Oh, my God, you didn't!
( shouts )
Then why didn't you tell me
that before?!
I tried, but people
kept coming in
and then you took
your breast out.
Whoa! Hey!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You saw her breast?
( whispers ):
I'll tell you about
it later. Be cool.
Then, Joey, what the hell
were you doing
with an engagement ring?!
It wasn't my ring.
It's Ross's ring.
That's why I felt
so bad, Rach
because he was
going to propose.
What?
You were going
to propose to me?
Uh...
No.
Well, this is awkward.
But I was going
to see if you maybe wanted
to start dating again
but I mean,
that was all, Rach.
Dude, step up.
I proposed.
No, you didn't.
Oh, that's right.
There's a lot
going on here
and I think I ate
some bad fruit earlier.
( knocking )
Hey, she just woke up.
She's hungry.
Why don't we give this
another try?
Okay.
I can't believe
you told her
I was going to propose.
I can't believe
you're not going
to propose.
Hey, I'm not going
to rush into anything.
Oh, yeah, dude,
I totally understand.
Usually after I have
a baby with a woman
I like to
slow things down!
Oh, my God!
What?
She's doing it!
She's breast-feeding, look.
Oh, it's beautiful.
I'll come back
for her later.
Okay.
Thank you.
Oh, wow, this feels weird.
Good weird?
Wonderful weird.
You know what,
you guys?
I'm going to go, too.
I'm sorry
about everything.
Honey, don't worry.
It was my mistake.
No, Rach, I should
have told you sooner.
It's just that...
Man, that kid is going to town!
She's perfect.
We're so lucky.
We really are.
Look, I know
it's not a proposal
and I don't know
where you are
but with everything
that's been going on
and with Emma...
I've been feeling...
I know. I know.
I'm feeling.
Yeah?
( laughs nervously )
Okay, well, that...
Wow, okay, well, um...
then, maybe, at least we
can talk about us again.
Yeah, maybe.
Well, good, okay.
I-I, kind of think,
you know, if we...
You're wearing
the ring.
Wh-What's that?
And you told Phoebe
you were engaged.
I'm sorry. What?
When you thought
Joey proposed, did...
did you say yes?
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Kids, I spoke to a doctor
and picked up these pamphlets
on how to get pregnant.
Hey, Dad.
Sorry to bother you again
but could you pass
my pamphlets back?
Thank you.